xcubelabs.com 2019-04-25

# PRIVACY POLICY - [x]cube LABS - Digital Transformation Company

PurpleTalk is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the PurpleTalk Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the PurpleTalk website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Collection of your Personal Information

PurpleTalk collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. PurpleTalk also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests, and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by PurpleTalk. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by PurpleTalk for the operation of the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the PurpleTalk Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through PurpleTalk public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Note: PurpleTalk does not read any of your private online communications.

PurpleTalk encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from PurpleTalk so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. PurpleTalk is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the PurpleTalk and PurpleTalk family of Web sites.

### Use of your Personal Information

PurpleTalk collects and uses your personal information to operate the PurpleTalk Web site and deliver the services you have requested. PurpleTalk also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from PurpleTalk and its affiliates. PurpleTalk may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

PurpleTalk does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. PurpleTalk may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, you are unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, PurpleTalk may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to PurpleTalk, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.PurpleTalk does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

PurpleTalk keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within PurpleTalk, in order to determine what PurpleTalk services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within PurpleTalk to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

PurpleTalk Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

(a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on PurpleTalk or the site;

(b) protect and defend the rights or property of PurpleTalk; and,

(c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of PurpleTalk, or the public.

### Where we hold and process your personal data

Some or all of your personal data may be stored or transferred outside of the European Union (the EU) for any reason, including for example, if our email server is located in a country outside the EU or if any of our service providers or their servers are based outside of the EU. We shall only transfer your personal data to organizations that have provided adequate safeguards in respect of your personal data and are GDPR Compliant.

### Tailoring your experience at the Site with relevant PurpleTalk materials

Understanding the Site’s user population, identifying subject areas of interest, and determining whether the Site is designed to work with the computer settings of a majority of our visitors Measuring and improving the effectiveness of PurpleTalk marketing programs across different channels.

### Improving our web content and navigation.

On the basis of your consent. So far as you have granted us consent to the processing of personal information for specific purposes (for example, your application form for employment with PurpleTalk), the lawfulness of such processing is based on your consent. You may withdraw your consent at any time.

(i) For compliance with a legal obligation. This includes anti-fraud and anti-money laundering measures as well as tax and social security requirements.

(ii) We will not sell, share, or rent or otherwise make available your personal information to other parties, except that we may disclose the information to third parties who perform services on our behalf and have a need to access the information in connection with those services. Any third parties will only process this information to the extent to which and within the limits that PurpleTalk itself is permitted to process that data. In addition, PurpleTalk may disclose your contact information in response to inquiries by bona-fide rights owners’ in connection with allegations of infringement of copyright or other proprietary rights arising from information that you have posted on the Site or otherwise provided to PurpleTalk.

### RETENTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

PurpleTalk retains your personal information for so long as is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which it was collected. We may retain your personal information for longer if they may be the subject of a legal claim, or may otherwise be relevant for future litigation.

### MARKETING

If, at any time, you prefer not to receive further communications from us in any or all forms you will have the ability to unsubscribe from such communications by means of a link provided in every e-mail that is sent to you by us. When subscribing to PurpleTalk e-mail newsletters, you are given the opportunity to select which promotions, news, and information you would like to receive at the time of sign up, and you will have the opportunity to unsubscribe from such communication

### Use of Cookies

The PurpleTalk Web site uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize PurpleTalk pages, or register with PurpleTalk site or services, a cookie helps PurpleTalk to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same PurpleTalk Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the PurpleTalk features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the PurpleTalk services or Web sites you visit.

### Security of your Personal Information

PurpleTalk secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. PurpleTalk secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

We use the following types of cookies:

“persistent cookies” to improve your experience when using the Site.

“session cookies” to enable your use of our Site and to remember your settings. Session cookies are deleted automatically at the end of your visit.

“web analytics cookies”. These cookies are used by us or third-party providers to analyze how the Site and our services are used, including the following types:

**Google Analytics** : This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies” to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google uses this information to evaluate your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website and accepting the use of the cookies, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. To find out more about Google Analytics, Google’s privacy policy and opting out of its cookies please visit: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

**Upshot.ai Analytics** : This website uses Upshot.ai, a web analytics and marketing service provided by Purpletalk. Upshot.ai uses HTTP “cookies” and similar technologies to collect information to measure and understand how users use this website. This includes user activity tracking on this website, including pages visited and links clicked. PurpleTalk does this to provide you with experiences and marketing messages based on your likely interests. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Site (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Upshot.ai. Upshot.ai may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Upshot.ai’s behalf. Upshot.ai will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Upshot.ai.

Web beacons. PurpleTalk includes a web beacon, which is a graphic image, in a majority of the HTML email messages we send. PurpleTalk uses web beacons, alone or in conjunction, with cookies to compile information about your usage of PurpleTalk websites and interaction with emails from PurpleTalk. We use the capability to determine whether or not an email has been received, opened, or when an URL has been clicked inside of an email that directs you to one of PurpleTalk’s websites. These web beacons are used to: (i) operate and improve PurpleTalk websites, services, and email communications, (ii) send emails in a format users can read and (iii) track the aggregate number of emails opened. The web beacon does not collect your personal information, however the information compiled by the web beacon allows us to tie a user to information PurpleTalk has collected in data collection process as set out in this Privacy Statement. You may refuse the use of web beacons by selecting the appropriate settings on your email program to disable image and refraining from clicking on any links in email messages.

By continuing to browse or use our Sites and services, you agree that we can store and access cookies and other tracking technologies as described herein.

### Security of your Personal Information

PurpleTalk secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. PurpleTalk secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

### Changes to this Statement

PurpleTalk will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. PurpleTalk encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how PurpleTalk is protecting your information.

### Contact Information

PurpleTalk welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that PurpleTalk has not adhered to this Statement, please connect@PurpleTalk.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES

This website contains links to other Web sites not operated by PurpleTalk.

PurpleTalk is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any non-PurpleTalk web sites to which we link from the Site. We are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you provide whilst visiting other websites and sites not governed by our Privacy Statement. We cannot control the content or security of such websites. We cannot be held responsible for any loss or damage incurred by a user as a result of visiting such websites. No links are intended to be, nor should be construed as, an endorsement of any kind by us of that other website.

### COMPLIANCE WITH LAW

PurpleTalk complies with all applicable privacy laws and regulations. PurpleTalk may be compelled to surrender personal user or customer information to legal authorities if presented with a court subpoena or similar legal or administrative order, or as required or permitted by the laws, rules and regulations of any nation, state or other applicable jurisdiction. Also, in the event of a violation of the terms and conditions of use of the Site or a violation of any restrictions on use of materials provided in or through the Site, we may disclose personal user information to our affected business partners or legal authorities.

### ACCESS RIGHTS

In accordance with applicable data protection laws, including but not limited to the GDPR, you have a right to request a copy of the personal information we hold about you and details of how we use that information. If any of the information held about you is incorrect or out of date, you have the right to amend or rectify it, please follow the process outlined below and we will amend our records where appropriate. You also have the right to require us to erase your personal data, stop processing your personal data, restricting the processing of your personal information, right of portability of your personal information and/or to withdraw your consent to processing. This may not apply if there are other legal justifications to continue processing. If you think we may have incorrect personal information, or would like a copy of the personal information we hold on you, or to exercise any other data protection right, please contact us. Please note that we need you to prove who you are before we can provide you with any information.

You also have a right to lodge a complaint with a relevant supervisory authority.

### CHILDREN

PurpleTalk understands the importance of protecting children’s privacy, particularly in their online interactions. This Site is not designed for and does not intentionally target or solicit to children 18 years of age and younger.

### USE OF PurpleTalk WEB SITES

Your access to and use of the Site are subject to this Privacy Statement and certain other terms and conditions, contained in our Terms and Conditions of Use.
